Register of the Young Americans for Freedom records
Hoover Institution Archives
Young Americans for Freedom records
1951-2010
2011C55
Hoover Institution Archives
80 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (32.4 linear feet)
Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, convention and meeting materials, newsletters, bulletins, leaflets, flyers, legal and financial records, membership records and mailings, printed matter, and audiovisual material relating to political conservatism in the United States and on American college campuses.
Young Americans for Freedom.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2011.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Historical Note
American ideologically conservative student and youth activism organization that was founded in 1960 as a coalition between traditional conservatives and libertarians on American college campuses.
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, convention and meeting materials, newsletters, bulletins, leaflets, flyers, legal and financial records, membership records and mailings, printed matter, and audiovisual material relating to political conservatism in the United States and on American college campuses.
United States--Politics and government--1945-1989.; United States--Politics and government--1989-; Conservatism.; Student movements--United States.
- Correspondence, 1961-2010
  - General, 1963-2010
    - 1963-1969 (Box-folder 1: 1)
      Scope and Contents note
      Includes correspondence with Spiro Agnew, Howard Baker, George H. W. Bush, and James Marin.
    - 1970-1979 (Box-folder 1: 2)
      Includes correspondence with Pat Buchanan, Bill Archer, and Jack Kemp.
    - 1980 (Box-folder 1: 3)
      Includes correspondence with William F. Buckley Jr., Bob Dole, and John A. Welborn.
    - 1981 (Box-folder 1: 4)
      Includes correspondence with James Watt.
    - 1982 (Box-folder 1: 5)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 1: 6)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 1: 7)
      Includes correspondence with William F. Buckley Jr., David Dreier, Edward Koch, Clarence Pendleton Jr., Phyllis Schafly, Jim Ellis, Newton Russell, and Ed Zschau.
    - 1985 (Box-folder 1: 8)
    - 1986 January-June (Box-folder 1: 9)
      Includes correspondence with Bob Dole.
    - 1986 July-December (Box-folder 2: 1)
      Includes correspondence with Daniel Manion, Senator Barry Goldwater, William F. Buckley Jr., and David Dreier.
    - 1987 January-June (Box-folder 2: 2)
      Includes correspondence with Pat Buchanan, Pat Nolan, Owen Johnson, and William F. Buckley Jr.
    - 1987 July-December (Box-folder 2: 3)
      Includes correspondence with Al McCandless, George Wortley, and William F. Buckley, Jr.
    - 1988 January-April (Box-folder 2: 4)
      Includes correspondence with Amo Houghton.
    - 1988 May-June (Box-folder 2: 5)
    - 1988 July-December (Box-folder 3: 1)
    - 1989 January-May (Box-folder 3: 2)
      Includes correspondence with Pat Buchanan.
    - 1989 June-December (Box-folder 3: 3)
    - 1990-1994 (Box-folder 3: 4)
      Includes correspondence with Dan Quayle.
    - 1995-1999 (Box-folder 3: 5)
      Includes correspondence with Bill Morrow, Mike Briggs, Elton Gallegly, and W. M. J. "Pete" Knight.
    - 2000-2001 (Box-folder 4: 1)
      Includes correspondence with Christopher Cox and Ron Paul.
    - 2002 January-July (Box-folder 4: 2)
    - 2002 August-December (Box-folder 4: 3)
    - 2003 (Box-folder 4: 4)
      Includes correspondence with William F. Buckley, Jr.
    - 2010 (Box-folder 4: 5)
    - Undated (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - Butler, Ed, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - Derham, Richard, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 4: 8)
  - Edison, Charles, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - Membership applications and prospects, 1986-2010 (Box-folder 4: 10-11, 5: 1)
  - Membership revocations, 1971 (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - National Advisory Board invitations, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 5: 4)
  - Washington Intelligence Bureau, 1987 (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - Werner, L. Rob, 1964-2010 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - White House, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Widener, Alice, 1968 (Box-folder 5: 8)
- Office File, 1960-2010
  - Advisory Board, 1963-1988
    - General, 1963-1970
      - Declinations, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 5: 9)
      - National Conference, 1966 (Box-folder 5: 10)
      - Resignations, 1963-1970 (Box-folder 5: 11)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1965-1988 (Box-folder 5: 12-13)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1966-1970
      - 1966 October 8-9 (Box-folder 6: 1)
      - 1967 January 7 (Box-folder 6: 2)
      - 1968 June 21-23 (Box-folder 6: 3)
      - 1969 February 28 - March 2 (Box-folder 6: 4)
      - 1969 June 20-22 (Box-folder 6: 5)
      - 1969 August 31 (Box-folder 6: 6)
      - 1969 October 3 (Box-folder 6: 7)
      - 1970 February 6-8 (Box-folder 6: 8)
      - 1970 July 24-26 (Box-folder 6: 9)
      - 1970 October 23-29 (Box-folder 6: 10)
    - Reports, 1978 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Board file, 1960-2003
    - General, 1960-2003
      - Conventions, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 7: 2)
      - Direct mail, 1980-2002 (Box-folder 7: 3)
      - Financial, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 7: 4-5)
      - Legal, 1984-2001
        - General, 1984-2001 (Box-folder 7: 6)
        - Contracts, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 7: 7)
        - Hazlett Estate, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 7: 8)
      - Subject file, 1960-2003
        - General, 1973-1995 (Box-folder 7: 9-10, 8: 1)
        - 1960-1979 (Box-folder 8: 2-3)
        - 1980-1989 (Box-folder 8: 4-6)
        - 1990-2003 (Box-folder 9: 1)
        - Heckman, Robert C., 1976-1977 (Box-folder 9: 2)
        - Sarcino, Bill, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 9: 3)
        - Young America's Campaign Committee, 1972 (Box-folder 9: 4)
      - Printed matter, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 9: 5-6)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1968-1997
      - Board mailings, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 9: 7)
      - Board of Directors memos, 1968-1994
        - 1968-1979 (Box-folder 10: 1-3)
        - 1980-1994 (Box-folder 10: 4)
      - Letters to the Board, 1978 (Box-folder 10: 5)
      - National Board memos, 1983-1997 (Box-folder 11: 1)
    - Meeting materials, 1972-1981 (Box-folder 11: 2-5)
    - Meeting minutes, 1963-2000
      - Board of Directors meetings, 1963-2000
        - 1963-1969
          - General, 1963-1969
            - 1963-1965 (Box-folder 12: 1)
            - 1966-1968 (Box-folder 12: 2)
            - 1969 (Box-folder 12: 3)
          - 1965 August 29 (Box-folder 12: 4)
          - 1965 October 24 (Box-folder 12: 5)
          - 1966 February 28 (Box-folder 12: 6)
          - 1966 March 19-20 (Box-folder 12: 7)
          - 1966 July 30 (Box-folder 12: 8)
          - 1967 March 17-19 (Box-folder 12: 9)
          - 1967 June 9-11 (Box-folder 13: 1)
          - 1967 October 6-8 (Box-folder 13: 2)
          - 1968 February 9-10 (Box-folder 13: 3)
          - 1968 April 20-21 (Box-folder 13: 4)
          - 1968 August 8 (Box-folder 13: 5)
          - 1968 November 8-10 (Box-folder 13: 6)
        - 1970-1979
          - General, 1971-1979
            - 1971-1973 (Box-folder 13: 7)
            - 1979 (Box-folder 13: 8)
          - 1971 February 5-7 (Box-folder 13: 9)
          - 1971 May 28-30 (Box-folder 13: 10)
          - 1971 September 4 (Box-folder 13: 11)
          - 1971 October (Box-folder 14: 1)
          - 1971 October 29-31 (Box-folder 14: 2)
          - 1972 February (Box-folder 14: 3)
          - 1972 February 4-6 (Box-folder 14: 4)
          - 1972 June (Box-folder 14: 5)
          - 1972 June 16-18 (Box-folder 14: 6)
          - 1972 September (Box-folder 15: 1)
          - 1972 December (Box-folder 15: 2)
          - 1972 December 1-2 (Box-folder 15: 3)
          - 1973 February 23-25 (Box-folder 15: 4)
          - 1973 May (Box-folder 15: 5)
          - 1973 May 25-27 (Box-folder 15: 6)
          - 1973 August 19 (Box-folder 15: 7)
          - 1973 October 5-7 (Box-folder 15: 8)
          - 1974 February (Box-folder 16: 1)
          - 1974 June 7-9 (Box-folder 16: 2)
          - 1974 October 11-13 (Box-folder 16: 3)
          - 1975 February 21-23 (Box-folder 16: 4)
          - 1975 June 13-15 (Box-folder 16: 5)
          - 1975 August 17 (Box-folder 16: 6)
          - 1975 September 12-14 (Box-folder 16: 7)
          - 1976 January 16-18 (Box-folder 16: 8-9)
          - 1976 May 28-30 (Box-folder 16: 10)
          - 1976 November 5-7 (Box-folder 17: 1-3)
          - 1977 February 6-7 (Box-folder 17: 4-5)
          - 1977 June 10-12 (Box-folder 17: 6)
          - 1977 August 28 (Box-folder 17: 7)
          - 1977 November 11 (Box-folder 17: 8)
          - 1977 November 11-13 (Box-folder 17: 9-10)
          - 1978 July (Box-folder 17: 11)
          - 1978 November (Box-folder 18: 1)
          - 1979 November (Box-folder 18: 2)
        - 1980-2000
          - 1980 (Box-folder 18: 3)
          - 1981 (Box-folder 18: 4)
          - 1982 (Box-folder 18: 5)
          - 1983 (Box-folder 18: 6)
          - 1987 (Box-folder 18: 7)
          - 1988 (Box-folder 18: 8)
          - 1997-2000 (Box-folder 18: 9)
      - Policy and finance meeting, 1966 (Box-folder 18: 10)
      - State Chairmen's conference, 1967
        - 1967 January 27-29 (Box-folder 18: 11)
        - 1967 June (Box-folder 18: 12)
    - Membership lists, 1972-1983 (Box-folder 18: 13)
    - Reports, 1970-1989
      - 1970-1979 (Box-folder 19: 1)
      - 1984 (Box-folder 19: 2)
      - 1985 (Box-folder 19: 3)
      - 1986 (Box-folder 19: 4-5)
      - 1987 (Box-folder 20: 1)
      - 1988 (Box-folder 20: 2)
      - 1989 (Box-folder 20: 3)
  - Chapter and member file, 1968-2009
    - Specific chapters, 1978-2001
      - Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn Chapter, Oklahoma State University, 1978 (Box-folder 20: 4)
      - Cal YAF, direct mail, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 20: 5)
      - Georgetown YAF, 1984 (Box-folder 20: 6)
      - Indiana YAF, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 20: 7)
      - Iowa YAF, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 20: 8)
      - Michigan YAF, 2001 (Box-folder 20: 9)
      - San Diego YAF, 1991 (Box-folder 20: 10)
    - Chapter applications, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 20: 11)
    - Chapter numbers and information, 1984-1994 (Box-folder 20: 12)
    - Manuals and materials, 1968-2009 (Box-folder 20: 13-14, 21: 1-3)
    - Membership lists, 1981-2000 (Box-folder 21: 4-6)
    - Membership applications, 1986-1998 (Box-folder 21: 7, 22: 1-2)
    - State registrations, 2001-2003
      - General, 2002 (Box-folder 22: 3)
      - District of Columbia, 2002 (Box-folder 22: 4)
      - Florida, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 22: 5)
      - Kentucky, 2002 (Box-folder 22: 6)
      - Maine, 2002 (Box-folder 22: 7)
      - Minnesota, 2001 (Box-folder 22: 8)
      - New York, 2001 (Box-folder 22: 9)
      - North Carolina, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 22: 10)
      - Pennsylvania, 2002 (Box-folder 22: 11)
      - South Carolina, 2001 (Box-folder 22: 12)
      - Tennessee, 2001 (Box-folder 22: 13)
      - Utah, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 22: 14)
      - Washington, 2002 (Box-folder 22: 15)
      - West Virginia, 2002 (Box-folder 22: 16)
  - Directories, undated (Box-folder 22: 17)
  - Drafts, letterheads, and forms, 1972-1987 (Box-folder 23: 1-4)
  - Leadership file, 1970-2010
    - General, 1986-2010 (Box-folder 23: 5-6)
    - Executive directors, 1970 (Box-folder 23: 7)
    - Field representatives, 2002 (Box-folder 23: 8-9)
    - Mailings, 1981 (Box-folder 23: 10)
    - State chairmen, 1972-2000 (Box-folder 23: 11, 24: 1)
  - Founding documents and bylaws, 1963-1995 (Box-folder 24: 2-7, 25: 1)
  - Memos, 1961-1995 (Box-folder 25: 2-8)
  - Minutes, 1973-1996 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Notes, 1961-2002 (Box-folder 26: 2-3)
  - Personnel file, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 26: 4)
    Contains business cards, resumes, and other printed matter.
  - Policy Committee file, 1962-1989
    - General, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 26: 5)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 26: 6)
    - Meeting minutes, 1971-1989 (Box-folder 26: 7)
    - Reports, 1962-1975 (Box-folder 26: 8-9, 27: 1)
  - Reports and manuals, 1969-2010 (Box-folder 27: 2-5, 28: 1-3)
  - Songs, songbooks, poems, 1971-1987 (Box-folder 28: 4-6)
  - Speeches and writings, 1962-2003 (Box-folder 29: 1-4)
  - Website (5/6/03), 2003 (Box-folder 29: 5)
  - YAF elections, 1971-1986 (Box-folder 29: 6-7)
  - Miscellany, 1970-2002 (Box-folder 29: 8-11, Box 30)
    Contains mailings, clippings, magazines, and other printed matter.
- Conventions and Events File, 1960-2010
  - General, 1970-2010
    News clippings, pamphlets, agendas, and other printed matter.
    - 1970-1979 (Box-folder 31: 1)
    - 1981-1983 (Box-folder 31: 2)
    - 1984-1985 (Box-folder 31: 3)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 31: 4)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 31: 5)
    - 1988-1989 (Box-folder 31: 6)
    - 1990-2010 (Box-folder 32: 1)
    - Undated (Box-folder 32: 2)
  - Anniversary events, 1970-1985
    Invitations, pamphlets, agendas, and other printed matter.
    - 10th Anniversary, 1970 (Box-folder 32: 3-4)
    - 20th Anniversary, 1980 (Box-folder 32: 5, 33: 1)
    - 25th Anniversary, 1985 (Box-folder 33: 2)
  - Conservative Political Action conferences, 1975-2009
    - 1975 (Box-folder 33: 3-4)
    - 1976-1979 (Box-folder 33: 5)
    - 1980-1983 (Box-folder 33: 6)
    - 1984-1986 (Box-folder 34: 1)
    - 1987-1989 (Box-folder 34: 2)
    - 1990-1998 (Box-folder 34: 3)
    - 2000-2009 (Box-folder 34: 4)
  - Great Elm conference, 1960 (Box-folder 34: 5)
  - National conventions, 1960-2010
    - 1960-1969 (Box-folder 34: 6, 35: 1)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 35: 2-3)
    - 1973-1974 (Box-folder 35: 4)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 35: 5, 36: 1)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 36: 2)
    - 1979 (Box-folder 36: 3)
    - 1981 (Box-folder 36: 4-5)
    - 1983-1987 (Box-folder 37: 1)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 37: 2)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 37: 3)
    - 1990-2010 (Box-folder 37: 4)
  - Regional conventions, 1971-2002
    - 1971-1988 (Box-folder 37: 5)
    - 1990-2002 (Box-folder 38: 1)
  - Sharon III conference, 1988 (Box-folder 38: 2-3)
- Direct Mail File, 1960-2002
  - Accounts and contracts, 1983-1989
    - General, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 38: 4)
      Contains invoices, contracts, correspondence, and other printed matter.
    - Bruce W. Eberle and Associates, 1983-1989 (Box-folder 38: 5-6)
    - Hugh C. Newton and Associates, 1989 (Box-folder 39: 1)
    - Response Dynamics, Inc., 1985 (Box-folder 39: 2)
    - Richard Delgaudio and Associates, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 38: 3)
  - Direct mail letters, 1968-2002
    - General, 1986-2001 (Box-folder 39: 4)
      News clippings, information sheets, and other printed matter.
    - Correspondence, 1986-2002
      - 1986-1995 (Box-folder 39: 5)
      - 2002 (Box-folder 39: 6-7)
    - Form letters, 1971-1998 (Box-folder 39: 8, 40: 1-5)
    - Mailing lists, 1986 (Box-folder 41: 1)
    - Responses, 1968-1998 (Box-folder 41: 2-5)
  - Initiatives and campaigns, 1960-2002
    - 1960-1969 (Box-folder 41: 6)
    - 1970-1979 (Box-folder 42: 1-2)
    - 1980-1984 (Box-folder 42: 3)
    - 1985 (Box-folder 42: 4)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 42: 5, 43: 1-2)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 43: 3-4, 44: 1-2)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 44: 3-4)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 45: 1)
    - 1990-1999 (Box-folder 45: 2)
    - 2000-2002 (Box-folder 45: 3)
    - Undated (Box-folder 45: 4-6)
- Financial Records, 1970-2010
  Expense reports, invoices, and other materials.
  - 1970-1973 (Box-folder 46: 1)
  - 1980-1985 (Box-folder 46: 2)
  - 1986 (Box-folder 46: 3)
  - 1987 (Box-folder 46: 4-5)
  - 1988 (Box-folder 46: 6, 47: 1-2)
  - 1989 (Box-folder 47: 3-5)
  - 1990-1991 (Box-folder 47: 6)
  - 1992-1997 (Box-folder 48: 1)
  - 1998 (Box-folder 48: 2)
  - 1999 (Box-folder 48: 3-5)
  - 2000 (Box-folder 48: 6, 49: 1-2)
  - 2001 (Box-folder 49: 3)
  - 2002 (Box-folder 49: 4)
  - 2003-2010 (Box-folder 49: 5)
- Legal Records, 1961-2010
  - General, 1961-2010
    - 1961-1989 (Box-folder 50: 1-2)
    - 1990-1999 (Box-folder 50: 3-4)
    - 2000-2010 (Box-folder 50: 5)
  - Accounts and contracts, 1984-1995 (Box-folder 50: 6)
  - Agreements, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 50: 7, 51: 1)
  - Bills, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 51: 2)
  - Lease, 1989-2000 (Box-folder 51: 3)
  - Specific cases, 1970-2002
    - California Supreme Court No. S074850, 1999 (Box-folder 51: 4-5)
    - Carmouche, Chris settlement, 2002 (Box-folder 51: 6)
    - Flaherty v. Lacy, Case No. 16-199-0073-83, 1983 (Box-folder 51: 7-8, 52: 1-10)
    - Flaherty v. Lacy, Civil Action No. 6931, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 53: 1-15, 54: 1-10, 55: 1-10)
    - Good v. University of Washington, 1973 (Box-folder 55: 11)
    - McCarthy v. Young Americans for Freedom, 2002 (Box-folder 56: 1-2)
    - McKee, Myron, 1992 (Box-folder 56: 3)
    - Taylor Estate, 1989 (Box-folder 56: 4)
    - Veed v. Schwartzkopf, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 56: 5)
    - Voegeli v. Illinois State University, 1973 (Box-folder 56: 6)
    - Wuelper v. University of New Hampshire, 1970 (Box-folder 56: 7)
- Printed Matter, 1951-2010
  - General, 1960-2010
    - 1960-1969 (Box-folder 56: 8)
    - 1970-1975 (Box-folder 56: 9)
    - 1976-1979 (Box-folder 57: 1)
    - 1980-1985 (Box-folder 57: 2)
    - 1986-1987 (Box-folder 57: 3)
    - 1988-1989 (Box-folder 57: 4)
    - 1990-1994 (Box-folder 57: 5)
    - 1995-1999 (Box-folder 57: 6)
    - 2000-2010 (Box-folder 58: 1)
    - Undated (Box-folder 58: 2-4)
  - Clippings, 1960-2010
    - Undated (Box-folder 58: 5)
    - 1960-1969 (Box-folder 58: 6)
    - 1970-1979 (Box-folder 58: 7)
    - 1980-1982 (Box-folder 59: 1)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 59: 2-4)
    - 1984-1985 (Box-folder 59: 5)
    - 1986 (Box-folder 59: 6)
    - 1987 (Box-folder 60: 1-2)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 60: 3-4)
    - 1989 (Box-folder 60: 5)
    - 1990-1995 (Box-folder 60: 6)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 61: 1)
    - 1997-1999 (Box-folder 61: 2)
    - 2000-2010 (Box-folder 61: 3)
  - Pamphlets and flyers, 1969-2001 (Box-folder 61: 4-6, 62: 1-6, 63: 1-5)
  - Petitions, undated (Box-folder 64: 1-5)
  - Press releases, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 64: 6)
  - Third party publications, 1951-1990
    - The American Conservative Union, 1976 (Box-folder 64: 7)
    - California Review, 1987 (Box-folder 64: 8)
    - CAP Political Maps, 1982 (Box-folder 64: 9)
    - Committee for a Responsible National Student Organization, undated (Box-folder 64: 10)
    - Committee of One Million, 1951 (Box-folder 64: 11)
    - The Conservative Party of New York County, 1971 (Box-folder 64: 12)
    - The University Star, 1990 (Box-folder 64: 13)
    - Youth Division Citizens for Reagan, undated (Box-folder 64: 14)
  - YAF publications, 1961-2010
    - Broadside, 1989 (Box-folder 64: 15)
    - California Collegiate Conservative, 1988 (Box-folder 64: 16)
    - California YAF, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 64: 17)
    - Campus Report, 1988 (Box-folder 65: 1)
    - Commentary on Liberty, 1969 (Box-folder 65: 2)
    - Convention Bulletin, 1973 (Box-folder 65: 3)
    - Creative Californian, 1979-1999
      - Undated-1979 (Box-folder 65: 4)
      - 1984-1986 (Box-folder 65: 5)
      - 1987 (Box-folder 65: 6)
      - 1988 (Box-folder 65: 7)
      - 1989 (Box-folder 65: 8)
      - 1994-1995 (Box-folder 65: 9)
      - 1997 (Box-folder 65: 10-11)
      - 1998 (Box-folder 65: 12, 66: 1-2)
      - 1999 (Box-folder 66: 3)
    - The Delaware Spectator, 1994 (Box-folder 66: 4)
    - Dialogue on Liberty, 1972-2002
      - Undated-1972 (Box-folder 66: 5)
      - 1975 (Box-folder 66: 6)
      - 1976 (Box-folder 66: 7)
      - 1977 (Box-folder 67: 1)
      - 1978-1979 (Box-folder 67: 2)
      - 1984-1989 (Box-folder 67: 3)
      - 1990-2002 (Box-folder 67: 4)
    - The Edifier, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 67: 5)
    - Freedom Fighter, 1987 (Box-folder 67: 6)
    - Free Campus News Source, 1972-1975
      - 1972 (Box-folder 67: 7-8)
      - 1973 (Box-folder 68: 1-2)
      - 1974 (Box-folder 68: 3)
      - 1975 (Box-folder 68: 4-5, 69: 1)
    - The Guardian Eagle, 1975-2002 (Box-folder 69: 2)
    - Hayward American, 1987 (Box-folder 69: 3)
    - The Indiana Intransigent, 1988 (Box-folder 69: 4)
    - The Intransigent, 1990 (Box-folder 69: 5)
    - Leadership Bulletin, 1981-1992
      - 1981-1990 (Box-folder 69: 6)
      - 1991 (Box-folder 69: 7-8, 70: 1)
      - 1992 (Box-folder 70: 2)
    - Libertas, 1987 (Box-folder 70: 3)
    - Liberty Today, undated (Box-folder 70: 4)
    - List of Un-American Organizations on Our College Campuses, 1989 (Box-folder 70: 5)
    - The Main Stream, 1994 (Box-folder 70: 6)
    - Manifest Destiny, 1983 (Box-folder 70: 7)
    - The Minutemen, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 70: 8)
    - National Student News Service, 1989 (Box-folder 70: 9)
    - Nemesis, undated (Box-folder 70: 10)
    - New Guard, 1979-2010
      - Undated-1979 (Box-folder 70: 11)
      - 1980-1985 (Box-folder 70: 12)
      - 1986 (Box-folder 70: 13-14)
      - 1988-1989 (Box-folder 70: 15)
      - 1990-1999 (Box-folder 70: 16)
      - 2000-2010 (Box-folder 70: 17)
    - New Intransigent, 1987 (Box-folder 70: 18)
    - The Orange County Option, 1986 (Box-folder 70: 19)
    - Public Affairs Division of YAF, 1961 (Box-folder 70: 20)
    - The Rational Anteater, 1990 (Box-folder 70: 21)
    - The Rational Individualist, 1969 (Box-folder 70: 22)
    - Rebels with a Cause, 1978 (Box-folder 70: 23)
    - Red Alert!, undated (Box-folder 70: 24)
    - San Diego YAF, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 71: 1)
    - The Sequent, 1986 (Box-folder 71: 2)
    - Underground newspaper guides, undated (Box-folder 71: 3)
    - Washington Inquirer, 1985 (Box-folder 71: 4)
    - YAF and the Right Scene, 1968-1995 (Box-folder 71: 5)
    - YAF in the News, 1969-1997
      - 1969 (Box-folder 71: 6)
      - 1971 (Box-folder 71: 7)
      - 1972 (Box-folder 71: 8)
      - 1973 (Box-folder 71: 9)
      - 1974 (Box-folder 71: 10)
      - 1975 (Box-folder 71: 11)
      - 1976 (Box-folder 71: 12)
      - 1977 (Box-folder 71: 13)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 72: 1)
      - 1981-1987 (Box-folder 72: 2)
      - 1996-1997 (Box-folder 72: 3)
    - YAF Update, 1981 (Box-folder 72: 4)
- Monographs, 1999-2010
  - A Generation Awakes, 2010 (Box 72)
  - Cadres for Conservatism, 1999 (Box 72)
  - The United States Since 1945, 2009 (Box 72)
- Audiovisual Material, 1953-2008
  - Photographs, 1953-2008
    - 1953 (Box-folder 73: 1)
    - 1962-1965 (Box-folder 73: 2)
    - 1966-1969 (Box-folder 73: 3)
    - 1970-1973 (Box-folder 73: 4)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 73: 5)
    - 1977 (Box-folder 73: 6)
    - 1978-1979 (Box-folder 73: 7)
    - 1980-1981 (Box-folder 73: 8)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 73: 9)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 73: 10)
    - 1985-1988 (Box-folder 73: 11)
    - 1990-1997 (Box-folder 73: 12)
    - 2002-2008 (Box-folder 73: 13)
    - Undated (Box-folder 73: 14-21, 74: 1-11)
    - Negatives, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 75: 1-5)
  - Posters, undated (Box-folder 75: 6)
  - Slides, 1983 (Box-folder 75: 7)
  - Cassettes, 1964-1987 (Box-folder 75: 8-10)
  - Floppy disks, undated (Box-folder 76: 1)
  - Video tapes, 1987 (Box 76)
- Memorabilia and Ephemera, 1971-2010
  - Bumper stickers, undated (Box-folder 76: 2-3, 77: 1)
  - Business cards, 2010 (Box-folder 77: 2)
  - Nametags, pins, and stamps, 1971-2010 (Box 81)
  - Miscellany, 1986 (Box-folder 77: 3)
    Letters, postcards, and other printed matter.
- Subject File, 1961-2003
  - American Council for World Freedom, 1972 (Box-folder 78: 1)